The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight,
and despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
It's finally time for us to go and train in the Heart Kingdom.
I swore I'd become worthy of Lady Phinnes' love
and earn my place as the head of the House of Vaud.
If I fail, it'll all be a lie.
The Spirit Guardians won't break even if I give it my all, right?
This'll be so much fun!
Yep. I'm gonna get seriously strong out there.
Get as tough as you want.
I'll still be way ahead of you, Magna.
You wanna bet?
I have to take out Magikula and avenge my mother.
But first, I need to build up my skills.
Come here.
Oh my boy
congratulations!
I wanted to know where you are with this,
and I think
this is a whirlwind,
this is very bright feltop Lagoon.
Let's approach it and just
永遠に惹かれる Shine like a diamond
天使と悪魔が交際してく
世界は矛盾だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで 負ける夢はダサい
そう何度も何度も
夢の前の壁を越えるさ
何度も何度も
弱さを未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に惹かれ
You shine like a diamond
サポートしています
初めも awさ
All he said was, I'll get stronger with my squad.
Weird.
Not sure why he didn't want to come with us. He obviously would have learned a lot.
Nah, Yuno's gonna get better no matter where he trains. I won't let him outdo me, though.
I see that you've all arrived.
We all appreciate the invitation, sir.
Come with me. The Queen is waiting.
I see a few new faces that I haven't had the pleasure of meeting.
Welcome to the Heart Kingdom.
Under normal circumstances, I would have ordered a magnificent feast to celebrate your visit, but unfortunately, it wasn't possible at this time.
It pains me that we cannot offer you more.
But please accept our greetings.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry. I know it's rude to interrupt, but that person resting in your lap...
Why, it's charming, obviously.
No, trust me. We know who it is. But what the heck is she doing here?
Sure. Wherever snacks be, you'll find me!
Sounds about right.
Must the black balls always be so unprofessional?
Maybe it's not such a big deal, though. Queen Lorpechka seems to be fine with it.
Well, if it's okay with the Queen, then it's okay with me.
She seems to be pretty relaxed for a monarch, doesn't she?
I don't know if relaxed is really the word I would use.
Brave magic knights of the Clover Kingdom, we are honored.
It's a privilege to be in your care.
Yeah, thanks for having us!
Now then, about your training. Gaja, would you please explain?
The first thing you all need to know is that Spade has already captured most of the Diamond Kingdom's bases,
and that their invasion is at a standstill for right now.
In other words, it won't be long before they decide to turn their focus on us or the Clover Kingdom.
To prepare for that, we will be subjecting each of you to rigorous training in order to accelerate your development.
Sounds good to me.
That's not a problem.
As you've explained, it is imperative that we improve quickly.
Then allow me to introduce the spirit guardians who will be teaching you.
Guardian of Earth, Sarado.
It's nice to meet you.
Guardian of Plants, Potroff.
Let's learn together!
Guardian of Fire, Floga.
Work up a sweat!
Guardian of Wind, Smearik.
They seem like a pretty serious crowd, huh?
Oh man, I can't decide which one of them I want to spar with most!
Captain Charlotte and Lady Mimosa, I would like you both to begin your training with Sarado.
Understood, sir.
We are ready.
Great, I'm looking forward to it!
Finral, you'll be learning from Smearik first.
Yes, sir!
Captain Rill, I'd like you to start with Potroff.
Alright, let's get to it!
I'll see you in the forest, then!
We'll be sticking to attributes for the rest of you.
The Fire Mages will work with Floga.
Don't go easy on me, you got that?
It seems you're both taking this seriously.
I can't wait to meet the two of you.
And you'll begin training with me, Luck.
As long as you put up a good fight, I don't care who I train with.
Hang on, don't you think you might be forgetting about somebody here?
I'm sorry, but you don't possess any mana.
Spirit Guardians are gifted, but we can't create power out of nothing.
Huh?
Well then, what was the point of me coming?
You're one of the Arcane Stage Mages, which means you'll give us an advantage against the Devil.
I would like you to face me in a battle, so that I can get a sense of your strength.
After that, we will decide how best to proceed.
Alright, looking forward to it.
As for the other Arcane Stage Fighter...
I will see you to Nero's training myself.
She'll be training directly with the Queen?
I'm very excited to work with you, Nero.
Undine and I will also be overseeing Noelle's training regimen.
Do your best!
Right, I'm ready.
That should cover all of our assignments.
Wait a second.
What's the matter, Magna?
Luck here.
You're always competing with each other.
Any way I can train under you too, so we can keep that going?
Fine by me.
Awesome!
Well, I don't really mind, but are you sure that you can hack it?
Of course I can!
I should mention, none of you are permanently bound by the assignments I've chosen for you.
Once your mana grows a bit, you'll move on to a different Spirit Guardian next to see what new insights they have to offer.
That way, you can learn even more.
Magic Knights, your training will begin now.
Please don't let us down.
Right!
Magna uses Flame Magic, and Luck uses Lightning Spells.
And both of those are natural things, which is how you guys like to fight here in the Heart Kingdom, right?
Which means these two should be perfect, shouldn't they?
On a basic level, I suppose.
First, I'll show you how you can use natural mana to create mana words.
Oh wow, what the hell is that?
It's a necessary skill for combat here.
When you build spells out of mana words, it allows you to add some simple commands into your magic techniques.
For example...
Huh?
Dodge this attack.
Okay.
Mana words will give the spell a more complex directive, such as become larger or pursue him.
That's nuts.
Cool.
Yeah, I want to learn that.
Plants grow from the earth.
To strengthen plant-based magic, you begin with the soil.
When you put it that way, I think I get what you're saying.
You're saying the first step is understanding the earth.
It's probably easier to explain if I give you a demonstration.
So this is what mages are capable of in the Heart Kingdom.
Our magic attributes may be different, but we all need to be in tune with nature to use our spells.
As soon as you have a good grasp on that, your abilities will begin to grow quite rapidly.
That was an impressive display.
Your magic type is similar to that of one of my subordinates, but it's much faster and far more powerful than hers is.
It seems you Clover Kingdom mages rely solely on your own mana, without making use of the natural mana that always surrounds you.
That sounds complicated, but we'll do our best.
How does it work?
Easy!
First you gather it all up from a big area with a cursed swoosh, then kablammo, you're good to go!
I'm sorry, but I think we'll need you to be more specific.
You sense the mana, like ding-ding-ding, then once you've got it, you have to go whoosh, you know?
Then we'll get into the technical stuff later.
I didn't get a word of that.
He's a little different.
The gusts from the mountains, the breeze off the ocean, it all passes through this valley.
Oh, okay. That must be why it's so windy here.
I have heard about the young man who was chosen by the wind spirit.
I was very eager to meet him.
Right! You mean Asta's rival.
But then you were sent here instead.
There must be a reason. I wonder.
I mean, I'm sure Gaja just figured we'd be a good match, is all.
Well, it's your move.
Is this training?
That's a dumb question, I know, but I really can't tell!
Whether this is for training or a real battle, the wind that blows between us remains the same.
Don't you agree?
I can't seem to figure this guy out.
What is he acting so intense for?
Spatial magic is mainly meant for supporting your friends.
That is what you believe, yes?
Yeah! And?
Well then, if an enemy targets you, do you expect your friends to come to your rescue?
Don't be a liability.
Your purpose is greater than that.
What the...
What will you do now?
Let me try again!
Very well. Wherever the wind may blow.
Ah, the weather's clear. Perfect day for training.
I look forward to working with you, Floga, sir.
First things first, let me see your magic ability.
Eighty percent should do it.
Flame magic!
Spiral flames!
All right, if this is what you can do at eighty percent, then I'd say you've got incredible potential.
That's nice, but if you ask me, this isn't nearly good enough.
I need to learn everything I can and get a whole lot stronger.
No way I'm gonna let this opportunity go to waste.
Understood.
Also, I hope this doesn't come off as rude.
But can you show me your powers, too?
Sorry, what?
That way I can judge for myself whether I can learn much from you.
Ah, that makes sense.
Okay, then.
So, that answer your question?
Yes, I should have never doubted your strength. I apologize.
Don't worry. I don't mind.
The flame was so intense. I want to do that myself.
Your potential is far greater than mine.
Once you learn how to harness natural mana, you shouldn't have any problem pulling off techniques that are even more impressive than I just showed you.
You will get there.
But gaining full control over natural mana is no easy feat.
Thank you so much for taking me under your wing!
Push! Push! You can do it!
Oh, man, come on!
As I thought, your magic is still too weak.
Too weak?
You're about at the fifth stage.
But in order to use these techniques in battle, you'll need to reach at least third stage or higher.
This is so much fun!
That one seems to have a knack for it.
Guess I'll get stronger without you, then.
Wait, Magna?
Just leave him alone, Asta.
If he can't get any better than he is right now, then he'll never be worth anything more than that.
Sorry to make you wait.
What?
As I mentioned earlier, I'd like us to fight so I can get a better sense of your ability.
Attack me with all your might.
I get to fight someone who's almost on par with the Wizard King.
Then may the best man win!
This is a good spot.
So what are you going to teach me first?
How to bask in natural mana.
All the plants and animals, the ground, water, wind, sunlight.
This place is filled to the brim with life, which means it's also rich with mana.
Now that you say something, I think I'm already getting a feel for it.
Good!
Never let go of that feeling.
You need mana words in order to master our techniques.
Listen close.
Once you become one with natural mana, you'll be able to use those words for spells.
That's amazing.
You know, just watching the creative way that you use your magic is giving me a serious burst of inspiration.
Then you should try it.
Use mana words however your heart desires.
It might not be perfect at first, but that's fine.
Okay.
Not bad.
There were no mana words, but...
The need to create is welling up inside me.
Wait, I've got an idea.
I can see that you're an excellent painter.
So let's try writing them this time instead.
Look, think, read, and write.
Like this?
Whoa, look at that.
Oh my.
And after only seeing them one time.
Well, don't stop now.
No, not the painting part.
Thanks for your help, Potrop.
I think this masterpiece will be even better because of you.
Not the point.
Hey, you're one of the black balls, right?
Actually, I know her as Queen Laura Petchka's pet.
Er, excuse me.
I mean her guest, of course.
Weren't you eating back at the palace?
Well, yeah, but I kind of sort of ate everything they had there,
so I figured I might as well go searching for new and undiscovered treats.
You're saying that you devoured all of the palace's supply?
Uh-huh.
All right, then.
Since you traveled all this way to the Heart Kingdom,
how would you like to learn some of our special combat techniques?
That doesn't really line up with my goal of eating all the delicious noms I can find.
Aw, don't be that way.
See? Look, these are called mana words.
They often come in handy.
Wow, we've got another prodigy.
But your execution could still use some work.
The secret to that is you have to be in touch with the natural mana.
There must be more succulent fruit somewhere in these woods!
I bet if we venture a bit deeper into the forest,
I'll find some scenery that really gets my creative juices flowing!
I'm begging you, just listen to me for a few minutes, please.
Queen Laura Petschka, we're ready to learn from you and Undine.
Of course.
But first, there's something I'd like to bring to your attention.
I need you to rescue me.
If nothing changes, I'll be killed by this curse.
And soon.
You'll be okay.
We'll stop the devil before that happens.
That's why we came here to train.
We are the ones who will defeat Magicula.
Sorry, could you explain what you mean by that?
Obviously, striking down the Spade Kingdom's invasion
will require the help of the other magic knights, but...
Magicula's inside someone.
An extremely powerful mage.
Her name is Vanica.
The only way we'll even stand a chance against a foe like her
is if Undine and I work together with the two of you.
And you already have an idea of what this Vanica person can do, is that it?
She sounds pretty tough.
Well, since I'm the Water Spirit,
it's my job to fight alongside the Queen and to protect her from danger.
But the two of us were no match for Vanica's astounding power.
Because of my weakness,
Her Majesty must live in fear of her impending death.
No, please don't ever blame yourself for my curse, Undine.
A person who has been possessed by a devil
cannot be defeated by normal means.
I get it.
So by teaming up with me and Nero,
you get some kind of special advantage that should be enough to stop her, right?
We can't be sure of that just yet.
But I've come to the conclusion that the four of us working together
creates the best possible scenario for victory.
Noelle, I hope the two of you will agree to cooperate with us
and save Lorpechka's life.
With Nero's arcane stage spells
and your combative spirit and fighting style.
If we four train hard,
then we'll become a formidable team.
And then hopefully,
we can overpower Vanica and Megicula.
All of that makes sense to me.
Nero, can we count you in too?
We're grateful.
No need for that.
Trust me.
I've my own reasons for wanting to be the one to kill Megicula.
Good.
Then we agree.
Let's begin our training.
Go ahead and don't hold back!
That's the right idea.
But if you can't figure out your opponent's attacks,
it won't help you.
Come on, Finral.
You can't support anybody like this.
Great work, ladies.
Just keep on using those monowords.
I know you'll get the hang of it eventually.
Gotcha this time!
The power to invalidate magic is second to nothing.
But you're too narrow-minded to use it to its full potential.
I'm not done!
A fighting style that relies solely on your grit and determination is not enough to sustain you forever.
To truly unleash your abilities, it's only logical that you use them to back up your allies as well.
Let me try one more time!
I suppose you won't be satisfied with that advice alone.
Day one and they're already running me ragged.
And it's not just me, it's all of us.
So, are you seeing any progress?
It looks like everybody's gotten the hang of the Heart Kingdom's special techniques.
If it's like this every day, I'd be surprised if we weren't crazy tough at the end.
Great.
Well, keep it up, then.
Right.
Looks like they're all working hard to push past their limits.
So, I guess I better up my game as well.
Well, keep it up.
Stop it.
Hey.
This is a living for you.
If you want to see a while, you greed, trust the blood at the end.
spar Docs
Love suit
or
全然届かなくても
信じる君はあがいて前を向いている
だから枯れないようにやらがって
描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと僕を呼ぶ声だ
しまして
僕を呼ぶ声だ
我々は
Since everybody's out there working their butts off, the hideout's actually quiet for once.
Black Clover, page 156, Awakening Powers.
I'm pushing as hard as I can, and I don't mean in the john, you idiot.